### RICHARD ADEYINKA, ADEYEYE

Address: Harjuniemenkatu 2, A5, 15300, Lahti Finland | Mobile: +358 44309 7615

E-mail: richard.adeyeye@outlook.com | Nationality: Finnish

### **Summary**

An execellent academic background in Information Technology and Chemical Engineering. Presently working on Cloud Computing and Information Security for my master's research work.

I have a passion for IT infrastructure and designing the state-of-heart Web Applications and Development. Good shell scripting, Networking, TCP/IP, Routing, Switching, NAT and Subnetting skills.

### Skills & Competencies

- ✓ Excellent Communication Skills in English
- ✓ Good hands-on experience using MySQL and Excel
- ✓ Basic Java Programming, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C/C++
- ✓ Network Administration
- ✓ Cisco Platforms 65xx, routers, switches configuration skills

### Experience

### TESTBIRDS, Germany (SEPT. 2016- PRESENT)

- ✓ Webpages Usability test, Bug tests and Test cases
- ✓ Mobile Applications Usability test, Bug tests and Test cases

### **SeaFocus Intelligent Hunt (March- June 2017)**

✓ Research work for Finnish Transport Agency: Optimisation and Utilisation of Various Telecommunication Capacities in Fairways

# Nigeria National Petroleum Cooperation, Atlas Cove Depot, Lagos, Nigeria (Jan 2005 – Aug. 2007)

- ✓ Petroleum products import data collection and processing
- ✓ Radio operator

#### **Education**

## M.Sc. (TECHNOLOGY): COMMUNICATION AND SYSTEMS ENGINEERING, UNIVERSITY OF VAASA (2015 - PRESENT)

✓ Major: Wireless Communication Engineering | Minor: Sustainable and Renewable Energy

# B. Sc. ENGR.: INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY, VAASAN AMMATTIKORKEAKOULU (2009-2014)

✓ Major: Telecommunication Engineering | Minor: Software Engineering and Mathematics

# B. Sc. ENGR.: CHEMICAL ENGINEERING, OBAFEMI AWOLOWO UNIVERSITY, ILE-IFE, NIGERIA (2001-2008)

✓ Environmental Engineering | Biotechnology

### **Certifications**

✓ CISCO Certified Network Associate (2009-2012)

### SOLOLEARN ONLINE COURSES

✓ jQuery Tutorial course (June 2017- Present) | PHP Tutorial course (June 2017- Present) | SQL Fundamentals course (June 2017- Present) | JavaScript Tutorial course (August 2016- Present) | C++ Tutorial course (August 2016- Present)

### Reference

### Ulla Keino

CEO, Chairman, Partner, SeaFocus, UK ART OY LTD

Tel: +358 400726072 | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ulla-keino-31477b9/

Email: ulla.keino@seafocus.fi